<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Root on Now with more interwebs.</title>
    <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Root on Now with more interwebs.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 13:32:25 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zorndorff.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Run home assistant in k3s - IOT for everyone - part 1</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/kubernetes-k3s-home-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 23:06:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/kubernetes-k3s-home-assistant/</guid>
      <description>As a new home owner and nerd, I&amp;rsquo;ve been leaning into the &amp;ldquo;smart home&amp;rdquo; trend. Naturally, this makes for a great excuse to tinker with the latest IOT technology and to experiment with distributed computing. What better test bed for working with the &amp;lsquo;Service Mesh&amp;rsquo; than coordinating micro-computer devices and sensors? To that end, I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to use Rancher&amp;rsquo;s IOT focused kubernetes distribution k3s. I plan to write more about my setup in the future but, for now I&amp;rsquo;d just like to share my configuration for running the HomeAssistant platform on kubernetes cluster with a zwave gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a homelab for kubernetes development</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/home_lab_cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 12:09:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/home_lab_cluster/</guid>
      <description>The problem Local development environments are full of tradeoffs. Do you optimize for ease of installation, or &amp;ldquo;production&amp;rdquo; environment fidelity? Do you seed a subset of your production data for testing, or do you generate random datasets? Should it each service(persistence, api, batch) in the application be optional when developing new features? If you&amp;rsquo;re like me, these considerations are often a stumbling block on the path to a working prototype.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting FeedMachine</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/starting_feedmachine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 09:35:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/starting_feedmachine/</guid>
      <description>awesomefeedmachine.com has been a side project of mine ever since google shutdown their rss service. I&amp;rsquo;ll be documenting my work on this project here. Now of course there are numerous rss readers apps out there, I just want to try rolling my own.
The Problem I haven&amp;rsquo;t yet completed a full rss reader project after years of tinkering. Unless you count my original version which I&amp;rsquo;ve lost the code for.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Cafenet</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/starting-cafenet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Aug 2018 14:46:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/starting-cafenet/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always wanted to start a project that could be considered a real contribution to my community. However, this is somewhat difficult without a lot of free time on your hands. That being said, I&amp;rsquo;m currently in staycation mode between jobs so I decided to hack together a service to address a need in my local area.
The Problem Semi-skilled service workers require training and experience to be effective. Conversely, these jobs are typically lower wage part-time jobs that are looked at as a transitional position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Aug 2018 12:09:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>Hey there, you&amp;rsquo;ve landed on my personal website.
##Welcome!##
I&amp;rsquo;ll be using this space to host my random experiments and ramblings. Follow along as I experience the joy of planning and hacking on random side projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>