<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>fun on Now with more interwebs.</title>
    <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/tags/fun/</link>
    <description>Recent content in fun on Now with more interwebs.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 23:06:03 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zorndorff.github.io/tags/fun/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Run home assistant in k3s - IOT for everyone - part 1</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/kubernetes-k3s-home-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 23:06:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/kubernetes-k3s-home-assistant/</guid>
      <description>As a new home owner and nerd, I&amp;rsquo;ve been leaning into the &amp;ldquo;smart home&amp;rdquo; trend. Naturally, this makes for a great excuse to tinker with the latest IOT technology and to experiment with distributed computing. What better test bed for working with the &amp;lsquo;Service Mesh&amp;rsquo; than coordinating micro-computer devices and sensors? To that end, I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to use Rancher&amp;rsquo;s IOT focused kubernetes distribution k3s. I plan to write more about my setup in the future but, for now I&amp;rsquo;d just like to share my configuration for running the HomeAssistant platform on kubernetes cluster with a zwave gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting a homelab for kubernetes development</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/home_lab_cluster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2019 12:09:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/home_lab_cluster/</guid>
      <description>The problem Local development environments are full of tradeoffs. Do you optimize for ease of installation, or &amp;ldquo;production&amp;rdquo; environment fidelity? Do you seed a subset of your production data for testing, or do you generate random datasets? Should it each service(persistence, api, batch) in the application be optional when developing new features? If you&amp;rsquo;re like me, these considerations are often a stumbling block on the path to a working prototype.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>