<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>projects on Now with more interwebs.</title>
    <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/categories/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in projects on Now with more interwebs.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zorndorff.github.io/categories/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Running Rust on Arm with docker</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/rust-api-server-on-arm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/rust-api-server-on-arm/</guid>
      <description>I have a small home lab kubernetes cluster running k3s from rancher labs. As part of that deployment, the traefik ingress controller is included. This post is first in a series where I muddle through exploring the traefik ingress using a rust webserver.
Covered in this post.  Rust workloads on k8s with ARM and Docker.  What will be running? Since my home lab cluster runs on 4 raspberry pi&amp;rsquo;s, some work will be needed to get a properly formatted image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Run home assistant in k3s - IOT for everyone</title>
      <link>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/kubernetes-k3s-home-assistant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 23:06:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zorndorff.github.io/posts/projects/kubernetes-k3s-home-assistant/</guid>
      <description>As a new home owner and nerd, I&amp;rsquo;ve been leaning into the &amp;ldquo;smart home&amp;rdquo; trend. Naturally, this makes for a great excuse to tinker with the latest IOT technology and to experiment with distributed computing. What better test bed for working with the &amp;lsquo;Service Mesh&amp;rsquo; than coordinating micro-computer devices and sensors? To that end, I&amp;rsquo;ve chosen to use Rancher&amp;rsquo;s IOT focused kubernetes distribution k3s. I plan to write more about my setup in the future but, for now I&amp;rsquo;d just like to share my configuration for running the HomeAssistant platform on kubernetes cluster with a zwave gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
